LUCA INNOCENTI

me@lucainnocenti.com

SUMMARY

Now I'm leading a team of Magento developer to create wonderfull eCommerce, helping our customer to let shine their products.

– Your eCommerce doen't convert enough visitor? – Your funnel don't directs enough customer to buy? In this 4 years of eCommerce I had a lot of situations like that, but enhancing: - categorization - usability - customer awareness is possibile to improve convertions.

I believe in continuous projects improvement and that every goal is reachable with focused work and details attention. The thing that i love the most is analize problem and find innovating and fitting solutions.

Do you want to talk with me about your projects? Contact me, will be a pleasure.

SKILLS

PHP Web Development E-commerce Web Services Java jQuery JavaScript Magento Apache HTML Web 2.0 Web Applications SEO Subversion Programming MySQL User Experience Online Marketing CVS JSP Usabilty Advanced CSS SOA Creative Ideas Creative Marketing Solutions CSS CMS **JSON** UML SQL Online Advertising MVC SOAP Stored Procedures Seo basics PostgreSQL DWR Wordpress Basic Photoshop Struts Zend Framework AJAX Front-end Development Database Design Nginx

EXPERIENCE

Sintra Consulting 09 / 2011 - Present

Frontend Developer & Ecommerce Magento chief developer

I'm managing a team of 6 people working on Magento and making the best ecommerce

CDC Point spa 07 / 2010 - Present

Consultant for CDC spa

Integration of interhosting with Microsoft CRM and develope of connection between CRM and NIC/Domain provider API.

Optimization of customer experience on e-commerce.

Sintra Consulting 05 / 2007 - 09 / 2011

Web developer Java and Php

Working on web product development (1MinuteSite, Infarmacia etc) and Websites.

Interfree 03 / 2009 - 12 / 2010

Developer for www.interhosting.it

Develop of the interhosting platform in PHP + WebService + Perl + Postgres stored procedures. Interhosting is an Italian hosting platform linked to Interfree web network and CDC spa's property.

Unicredit Global Information Services

10 / 2008 - 12 / 2008

Java developer

I worked on the project ARENA.

EDUCATION

Università degli Studi di Firenze

2002 - 2007

105, Computer Science

Liceo Scientifico 1997 - 2002

86/100, English, Philosophy

INTERESTS

music, scouting, swimming, programming, SEO, project management, cooking, playing bass, playing guitar, theater, martial arts

ASSOCIATIONS

Agesci

LANGUAGES

Italian (Native or bilingual proficiency)

English (Professional working proficiency) French (Elementary proficiency)

Spanish (Elementary proficiency)